Guide to the Rice University Past Faculty and Staff records, 1961-1996 UA 008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1946-2013, 170648
  - Mersereau, Rebecca - Art and Art History, 1991-1997; 170930 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Merwin, John - Civil and Environmental Engineering, 1955-1998; 170931 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Merz, Monika - Economics, 1994-2001; 170932 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Michel, Curt - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1963-2000; 170933 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Miele, Angelo - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science (1 of 3), 1964-2011; 170934 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Miele, Angelo - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science (2 of 3), 1964-2011; 170935 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Miele, Angelo - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science (3 of 3), 1964-2011; 170936 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Mieszkowski, Peter - Economics, 1979-2009; 170937 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Miettinen, Hannu - Physics and Astronomy, 1977-2009; 170945 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Milburn, Ellsworth - Shepherd School of Music, 1975-2000; 170946 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Minter, David - English, 1967-1980, 1990-2002; 170947 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Mucha, Waclaw Jerzy - Russian Studies, 1990-1998; 170948 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Murray, William - Shepherd School of Music, 1992-2003; 170949 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Mutchler, Gordon - Physics, 1968-2008; 170950 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Naficy, Hamid - Art History, 1993-2006; 170951 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Nakatani, Hajime - Art History, 2002-2004; 170952 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Nalepa, Monika A. - Political Science, 2005-2008; 170953 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Nirenberg, David - History, 1992-2000; 170954 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Norcross, Alastair - Philosophy, 2002-2007; 170955 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Nordgren, Ronald P. - Civil and Environmental Engineering, 1989-2000; 170956 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Oberlack, Uwe - Physics and Astronomy, 2001-2010; 170957 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - O'Connor, Kathleen - Psychology, 1994-1997; 170958 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - O'Dell, Charles Robert - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1982-2000; 170959 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Odhiambo, Atieno E. S. - History, 1989-2009; 170960 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Ohno, Yuka - Economics, 1997-2002; 170961 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Oliver, Douglas E. - Architecture, 1997-2013; 170963 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Osherson, Daniel - Psychology, 1997-2003; 170962 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Pai, Vijay S. - Computer Science, 2000-2004; 170964 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Palmer, Graham - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 1974-2000; 170965 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Papanicolaou, Andrew C. - Psychology, 1999; 170966 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Park, Joon Y. - Economics, 2002-2006; 170967 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Payne, Jason K. - Architecture, 170968 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Pearlman, Michael D. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1979-2001; 170969 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Pearson, Deborah A. - Psychology, 1991-2013; 170970 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Pearson, J. Boyd, Jr. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1965-1999; 171097 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Perry, John - Shepherd School of Music, 1983-1999 [?]; 171098 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Pfeiffer, Paul E. - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1947-1997; 171099 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Pharr, George - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1979-1998; 171100 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Phillips, Scott - Sociology, 2003-2005; 171101 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Philpott, Charles W. - Biology (1 of 2), 1964-1996; 171102 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Philpott, Charles W. - Biology (2 of 2), 1964-1996; 171103 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Piper, William Bowman - English, 1969-1989; 171104 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Platner, Edward B. - Physics and Astronomy, 1996-2002; 171105 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Poindexter, Hally - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1965-1998; 171106 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Polanyi, Livia - Linguistics, 1988-1999; 171107 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Polking, John C. - Mathematics, 1968-2004; 171108 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Porterfield, Todd - Art and Art History, 2001-2002; 171109 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Potts, Geoffrey - Psychology, 1998-2006; 171110 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Poulos, Basilios - Art and Art History, 1975-2008; 171111 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Quenemoen, Caroline K. - Art and Art History, 2001-2010; 171112 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Quiñones, Miguel - Psychology and Management, 1993-2003; 171113 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Rabson, Thomas A. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1959-2002; 171114 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Ramaswamy, Balasubramaniam - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1989-1996; 171115 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Rame, Marcelo - Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1995-1997; 171116 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Ramnath, Sundaresh - Accounting, 1996-2001; 171117 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Rankine, Graeme - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1989-1995; 171118 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Rarick, Janet - Shepherd School of Music, 1992-2013; 171119 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Rau, Hsiu-hua Annie - Economics, 1992-1994; 171120 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Ray, Mary Ann - Architecture, 1995-1999, 2004; 171121 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Rea, Joan - Spanish, 1968-2000; 171122 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Redwine, Shirley - General Counsel, 1990-2001; 171123 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Reed, William - Political Science, 2002-2010; 171124 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Riedi, Rudolph - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1998-2008; 171125 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Rifai, Hanadi S. - Civil and Environmental Engineering, 1994-1999; 171126 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Rimberg, Alexander J. - Physics, 1997-2004; 171127 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Ritscher, Karen - Shepherd School of Music, 1999-2006; 171128 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Ro, Tony - Psychology, 1999-2008; 171129 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Roediger, Henry L., III - Psychology, 1988-1996; 171130 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Rogers, William E. - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1998-2005; 171131 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Rolnick, Claire - Hispanic and Classic Studies, 1995-1999 [?]; 171132 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Roman, Francisco J. - Jones Graduate School of Management, 2003-2007; 171133 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Roush, Sherrilyn - Philosophy, 1999-2006; 171135 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Roy, Lindy - Architecture, 1995-1998; 171136 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Rudolph, Frank Byron - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 1972-2003; 171137 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Rupp, George - Religious Studies/University President (photographs), 1985-1993; 171138 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Ryan, Frank - Mathematics/Vice President for External Affairs (1 of 3), 1990-1995; 171139 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Ryan, Frank - Mathematics/Vice President for External Affairs (2 of 3), 1990-1995; 171140 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Ryan, Frank - Mathematics/Vice President for External Affairs (3 of 3), 1990-1995; 171141 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Salaberry, Rafael - Hispanic Studies, 2000-2006; 171287 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Samuels, Danny Marc - Architecture, 1975, 1981-2013; 171290 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Sass, Ronald L. - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology (1 of 2), 1958-2005; 171291 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Sass, Ronald L. - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology (2 of 2), 1958-2005; 171292 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Sauerbrey, Roland - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1986-1994; 171293 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Schaffer, Alejandro - Computer Science, 1988-1996; 171297 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Scherer, William N. - Computer Science, 2006-2009; 171300 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Schneider, David - Psychology, 1989-2009; 171302 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Schnietz, Karen - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1994-2003; 171303 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Schnoebelen, Anne - Shepherd School of Music, 1974-2004; 171304 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Schroepfer, George - Biochemistry and Cell Biology (1 of 3), 1972-1998; 171309 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Schroepfer, George - Biochemistry and Cell Biology (2 of 3), 1972-1998; 171312 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Schroepfer, George - Biochemistry and Cell Biology (3 of 3), 1972-1998; 171314 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Seed, Patricia - History, 1982-2006; 171317 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Shanks, Jacqueline - Chemical Engineering, 1988-1999, 2001-2013; 171318 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Sharon, Eva O. Danielle - Linguistics, 1997-2000; 171321 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Shea, Louisa - French Studies, 2003-2007; 171322 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Sherman, Daniel - French and History, 1990-2001; 171325 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Sherman, William H. - Architecture, 1986-1994; 171327 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Shirley, Dennis - Education, 1988-1998; 171338 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Shockley, Richard - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1992-1996; 171339 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Simos, Panagiotis - Psychology, 1999; 171340 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Sisson, Virginia - Geology and Geophysics, 1992-2001; 171341 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Smith, George - Art and Art History, 1981-2010; 171342 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Gordon W. - Ecomonics, 1968-2002; 171343 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Ken - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1993-2005; 171344 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Marie-Christine - French Studies, 1996-1997; 171345 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Sneider, Allison L. - History, 2000-2008; 171346 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Soley, David - Shepherd School of Music, 1999-2001; 171347 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Sood, Sanjay - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1998-2002; 171348 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Spence, Dale W. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1963-2003; 171349 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Spencer, Albert F. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1994-1997; 171350 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Stabell, Richard - Dean of Admission and Records, 1973-2003; 171351 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Stasney, Richard C. - Linguistics, 1995-1999; 171352 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Stebbings, Ronald F. - Space Physics and Astronomy/Vice President for Student Affairs, 1968-1995; 171353 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Stemmer, Susanne - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1999-2002; 171354 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Stice, Earl K. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1990-1996; 171355 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Stingley, Robert - Mathematics, 1995-1998 [?]; 171356 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Stokes, Gale - History (1 of 2), 1967-2007; 171357 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Stokes, Gale - History (2 of 2), 1967-2007; 171358 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Stong, Richard - Mathematics, 1993-2007; 171359 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Stormer, John C., Jr. - Geology, 1983-1995; 171360 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Strassmann, Diana L. - Economics (1 of 2), 1983-2013; 171361 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Strassmann, Diana L. - Economics (2 of 2), 1983-2013; 171362 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Subtelny, Stephen - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1968-2000; 171580 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Sullender, Barry W. - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1996-2009; 171658 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Sullivan, Sonja R. - Philosophy, 1990-1994 [?]; 171660 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Sutton, Jonathan - Philosophy, 1998-1999; 171664 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Talwani, Manik - Geology and Geophysics, 1985-2006; 171666 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Taylor, Julie - Anthropology, 1981-2005; 171668 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, Ronald N. - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1983-2009; 171670 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Tebeaux, Elizabeth - Managerial Studies, 1995-1998; 171672 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Terk, Michael - Civil Engineering, 1996-2004; 171673 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Temkin, Larry - Philosophy, 1980-2000; 171675 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Thal, Sarah E. - History, 1999-2005; 171681 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Thomas, David O. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1990-1995; 171683 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Thombs, Lori A. - Statistics, 2000-2001; 171684 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Thornhill, Alan D. - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1996-2001; 171686 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Tikoff, Basil - Geology and Geophysics, 1997-1998; 171688 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Tileston, Jackie - Art and Art History, 1997-1998; 171690 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Todd, Anderson - Architecture, 1949-1992; 171692 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Torczon, Linda - Computer Science, 1985-2013; 171694 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Torres, Jorge H. - Bioengineering, 1998-2002; 171695 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Trammell, George - Physics, 1961-1993; 171697 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Trepel, Shirley - Shepherd School of Music, 1975-1994; 171702 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Turner, Elizabeth - History, 1997-1998; 171704 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Underwood, Shane E. - Jones Graduate School of Management, 2004-2009; 171705 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Urrutibéheity, Hector - Hispanic and Classical Studies, 1967-2000; 171706 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Vail, Peter R. - Geology and Geophysics, 1986-2001; 171707 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - van Delden, Maarten - Hispanic and Cultural Studies, 1997-2007; 171708 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Vandiver, Frank E. - Provost/History, 1955-1979; 171709 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Van Helden, Albert - History, 1970-2001; 171710 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Vella, Francis - Economics, 1990-1997; 171711 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - von der Mehden, Fred - Political Science, 1968-1997; 171712 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Walker, Ian D. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1989-1997; 171713 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Walker, James B. - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 1964-1995; 171714 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Wallace, Kristine Gilmartin - Classics, 1969-2006; 171715 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Walters, Geoffrey King - Physics, 1963-2006; 171716 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Wang, Chao-Cheng - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science/Computational and Applied Mathematics, 1968-2000; 171717 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Wang, Fu-Kuo Albert - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1998-2005; 171718 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Ward, Daniel S. - Political Science, 1990-1997; 171719 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Watanabe, Masahiro - Jones Graduate School of Management, 2003-2009; 171720 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Watenpaugh, Heghnar - Art and Art History, 1998-2001; 171721 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Watkins, Michael - Psychology, 1980-2007; 171722 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Weigelt, Carmen B. - Jones Graduate School of Management, 2003-2007; 171723 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Weischeit, Jon Carleton - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1987-1999; 171725 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Wells, Raymond O., Jr. - Mathematics (1 of 2), 1965-2000; 171727 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Wells, Raymond O., Jr. - Mathematics (2 of 2), 1965-2000; 171729 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Westphal, Sarah - German Studies, 2003-2009; 171730 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Wheeler, Mary Fanett - Mathematical Sciences, 1971-1995; 171731 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Whitaker, Gilbert R. - Jones Graduate School of Management, 1997-2007; 171732 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Whitford, Andrew B. - Political Science, 1997-2001; 171734 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Wiesner, Mark R. - Civil and Environmental Engineering, 1988-2010; 171736 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Wilbratte, Barry J. - Economics, 1989-1995; 171737 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Series VIII: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1947-2013, 171797
  - Imaambekov, Adilet - Physics, 2009-2012; 171742 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Leeds, J. Venn, Jr. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1964-1989; 171745 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Lewis, Edward S. - Chemistry, 1947-1990; 171747 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Smith, Richard - History, 1973-2013; 171795 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Winningham, Geoffrey - Visual and Dramatic Arts, 1969-2013; 171796 (Box 43, Folder 25)